Guide to the Living Stage records 1965-2001
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center.
- Series 1: Administrative and financial files, 1965-2000
  - Policies, planning, and development, 1967-2000
    - Robert Alexander Day, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Robert Alexander Day (RAD), 1982 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Sample Residency Proposal, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Search For New Space, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Season Archives, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Season Calendar, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Season Report, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Season Summary by R. Alexander, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Season Summary, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Season Summary, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Season Summary, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Season Summary, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Second Floor Renovation and School Press Release, November 1989 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Seniors, August 31, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Seven Stages, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Short Term Plan, 1981-1983 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Special Events, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Statewide Outreach Project, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Strategic Planning Group, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Summer Workshop Market Analysis, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - T Street Dossier, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - T.C.G, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Teen Mom Letters - Archives Fact Sheet - Schedule, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Teen Moms, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Teen Mother Proposal, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Teen Mothers - Narrative, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Teen Mothers of Today Redbook, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Teen Mothers of Today Redbooks, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Teen Mothers Project Fact Sheet, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Theatre Communications Group Registration, 1977-1979 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Theatre Communications Group, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Theatre Project Planning, 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - TMOT - "The Hearts and Minds of Young Mothers", 1994 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - TMOT Assessment, 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Training Program Draft, Undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Transcript of Living Stage Workshop and Interviews with Lillian Barns and Oran Sandel, Undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Transcript of Robert Alexander at AU, Undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Tri School Program, Spring 1967 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Tri School Program, 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Utrecht Paper on Ed. Drama, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Vanessa's Residency Update, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Packages Meeting, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Wendy's Report on the Impact of the Residencies, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - White House - Commission on Mental Health, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Youths in Arts Project, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Grants and foundations, 1967-1997
    - 25th Season Anniversary Benefit, April 22, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Africa Proposal Grant Request, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - April Trust, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - April Trust, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Arcana Foundation, 1991-1995 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Barney Neighborhood House Donation, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Benefit, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Benefit, May 20, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Benefit, General, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Benefit Budget, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Benefit Production, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Benefit, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Brooks Foundation, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Building Purchase, 1984-1986 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Building Purchase, 1984-1986 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Burton Bettingen Corporation, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Cafritz Foundation Request, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Chadwick, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Chadwick Fund, 1981-1982 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Children's Defense Fund, May 8, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Community Services for Deling Proposal: REP#JA/84718, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Contribution Information, 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Coors Proposal, 1989-1990 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Corina Higginson Trust, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - USA/CSP, 1984-1985 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - CSP, 1985-1986 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - CSP - File I, 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - CSP - File II, 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - CSP Files I, 1987-1988 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - D.C Arts Commission Grant Applications, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - D.C Artworks Grant Info, 1988-1989 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - D.C Recognition Grant, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - D.C Commission on the Arts and Humanities, 1975-1976 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - D.C Commission on the Arts, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - D.C Common Arts Grant Application, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - D.C Commission, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - D.C Commission on the Arts End of the Year, November 30, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - D.C Commission on the Arts Application and Proposal, 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - D.C Commission, 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - D.C.C.A.H Grant, 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - D.C.C.A.H Recognition and Inst. Building Grants, March 1981 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - D.C Commission, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - D.C Commission, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - D.C Commission on Arts/Humanities/Special Constituencies, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - D.C Humanities Grant, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - D.C.C.A.H Special Constituencies, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - D.C Commission, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - D.C Inter Agency, 1982-1984 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - D.C Comm - Prison, 1982-1987 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - D.C Comm - Impact Funding, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - D.C Comm - Special Const[ituencies], 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - D.C Human Services, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - D.C Comm Impact, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - D.C.C.A.H Impact Building, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - D.C Comm Recognition, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - D.C Comm Special Const[ituencies], 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - D.C.C.A.H Special Constituencies, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - D.C.C.A.H Special Constituencies Final Report, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - D.C.C.A.H Impact/Recognition, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - D.C Grants in Aid, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - D.C Special Const[ituencies], 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - D.C.C.A.H Impact/Recognition Application, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - D.C.C.A.H Special Constituencies, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - D.C Comm Special Const[ituencies], 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - D.C Public Schools Contract Information, 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - D.C.C.A.H Grants-in-Aid Support Materials, 1987-1990 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - D.C Commission on the Arts, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - D.H.S Final Report, 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - D.H.S Project, 1984-1985 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - D.H.S., 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - D.H.S., 1984-1985 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - D.O.E. Budget and Letters of Support, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Dear Martha Fundraiser, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Department of Education Grant File, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Department of Education Grant File, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Department of Education Hew Grant, 1981-1982 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Department of Human Services Report and Loan, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - DOE Proposal, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - DOE Proposal Draft, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - DOE Proposal Draft, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - DOE-Hew, 1982-1983 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - DOE-Hew, 1982-1983 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - DOE-Hew, 1982-1983 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Expansion Arts, 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Expansion Arts Proposal, 1978-1979 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Expansion Arts, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Exxon, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Exxon, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Exxon Grant, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Favrot Fund, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Favrot, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Favrot, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Federal Assistance Application, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Ford Grant, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Ford Foundation, 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Ford [Grant], 1984-1985 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Foundations, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Foundations, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Foundations, 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Foundations, 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Foundations, 1979-1980 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Foundations, 1980-1981 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Foundations, 1981-1982 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Foundations, 1982-1983 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Foundations, 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Foundations, 1984-1985 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Foundations, 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Foundations, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Foundations, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Foundations, 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Foundations, 1989-1990 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Foundations, 1990-1991 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Fundraising, 1970-1980 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Fundraising, 1977-1980 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Fundraising, 1979-1982 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Grant Application, 1970-1971 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Grant Application Forms, Undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Grants, 1976-1978 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Grants, 1976-1979 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Grants, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Grants - Dept. of Education, Proposals (Notes, Resources, Criteria), 1988 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Grants - Misc Faxes, Memos, Correspondence, 1980s-1990s (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Grants and Proposals, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - H.E.W, 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - H.E.W, 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - H.E.W, 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Handicapped Research Grant Request, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Hasbro, 1986-1992 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Hasbro (Children First - Yr 1), 1994-1995 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Hasbro (Children First - Yr 2), 1995-1996 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Hasbro Proposal and Report, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Hasbro Release Grant, November 1985 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Hearst Foundation, 1996-1997 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Hew Handicapped, 1980-1981 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Hew Juvenile, 1980-1982 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Hew Model Curriculum, 1980-1981 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Hexagon Beneficiary, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - I.B.M, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - IAY Washington Drama Society, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Inter-Agency Youth, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Intergenerational Project, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Letters to Foundations, 1969-1974 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - M.H.S.R, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Marpat Foundation, 1992-1997 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Meyer Foundation, 1987-1990 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Misc Commission and Service Details, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Misc Single Grants and Donations, 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Misc Small Grants/Donations, 1980-1983 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Misc. Small Grants, 1983-1984 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Nathan Cummings, 1995-1996 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1967-1968 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - NEA Award and Guidelines, 1967-1972 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - NEA Proposals, Budgets, and Schedules, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - National Endowment Grant, 1971-1972 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - National Endowment Grant Requested, 1972-1973 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - National Endowment Request, 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - NEA, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - NEA, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - NEA Expansion Arts - $10,000, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - NEA Request, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - NEA Request, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - NEA Grant Application, 1977-1978 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - NEA Grant, 1978-1979 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - NEA Proposal - Theatre Program, 1978-1979 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - NEA - Expansion Arts/Proposal and Application, 1979-1980 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - NEA Proposal - Theatre Program, 1979-1980 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - NEA, 1980-1981 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - NEA Expansion Arts Proposal, 1980-1981 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - NEA Theatre Program Proposal, 1980-1981 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - NEA Expansion, 1981-1982 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - NEA Expansion Arts, 1981-1982 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - NEA Reg[ulations], 1981-1982 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - NEA Special Constituencies, 1981-1982 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - NEA Special Constituencies/Grant Application, 1981-1982 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - NEA Theatre Program Grant Application, 1981-1982 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - NEA Hodsoll Grant, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - NEA Expansion, 1982-1983 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - NEA Expansion, 1982-1983 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - NEA Regular Grant, 1982-1983 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - NEA Theatre Program, 1982-1983 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - National Endowment, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - NEA Regular, 1983-1984 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - NEA Special Constituencies, 1983-1984 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - NEA Special Constituencies, 1983-1984 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - NEA Special Constituencies Interim Report, 1983-1984 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - NEA Special Constituencies Final Report, 1983-1984 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - NEA Special Constituent Grant Final Report, 1983-1984 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - NEA Theatre, 1983-1984 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - NEA Ensembles, 1983-1986 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - NEA Expansion Arts Fiscal, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - NEA Expansion, 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - NEA Expansion Arts, 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Newman's Own, 1994-1995 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - OHS, 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Old NEA Proposal, 1982-1984 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - OPEC Grant Correspondence, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Orthopedically Handicapped Ages 4-8, 1978-1981 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Other Than D.C School Grant, 1967-1968 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Ottinger Charitable Trust, 1994-1995 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Prince Charitable Trust, 1989-1994 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Proposal - National Black Police Association, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Proposal to W.K. Kellogg Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Public Welfare Foundation, 1994-1995 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller Grant, 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller Grant Application, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Sharpe Health Grant Application, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Sharpe Health Grant Requests, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Special Education Grant, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Spindle Top, 1980-1981 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Spindletop Foundation, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Spindletop Foundation, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Spunk, 1995-1996 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Stewart Trust, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Stewart Trust Grant Release, June 1986 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Strong Application, 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Strong Foundation Grant, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Theatre Communications Group, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - United Way, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Walton, Frances R., 1981-1982 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - YAP - Youth Awareness Program Grant, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Financials and correspondence, 1965-1996
    - 18th Season Benefit, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - 2F Correspondence Post Director A.S, 1965-1975 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Accounts, 1966-1979 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - ADASA Budget, 1990, 1991, 1993-1994 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - ADASA Finances, 1988-1990 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - ADASA Reconciliations, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Administration and Personnel Financials, 1985-1987 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - AMHA - George Mason Letters, June 8, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Angels, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Ann Roberts Alternatives, Inc - Summer Workshop, September 17, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Annandale United Methodist Church, April 29, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Arts for the Aging, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Associate Letters, circa 1982 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Audit, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Benefit, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Benefit, 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Benefit, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Benefit, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Benefit, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Benefit, 1990-1991 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Benefit, 1994-1995 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Benefits Newsletter, circa 1980s (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Bettye Richardson, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Bill Young Letters, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Board Committee Correspondence, 1979-1983 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Bobbi Snow Letter, August 11, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Bob's Christmas Card, 1986-1993 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Bob's Memos, 1970-1978 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Bob Alexander to T. Fichandler - Season Recap, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Boston University, Goddard/Cambridge, December 6, 1972 and September 10, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Breakfast, 1990-1991 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Bucks County, Keane College, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Budget, 1966-1968 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Budget, 1968-1969 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Budget, 1969-1976 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Budget - Rewrites, 1980-1982 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Budget, 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Budget, 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Budget - Accounts, 1981-1984 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Budget, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Budget - and Financial Documents, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Budget, 1984-1985 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Budget - Updates, 1984-1985 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Budget - Corrections Done, 1984-1989 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Budget - Information, 1986-1987 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Budget - Information, 1987-1988 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Budget - Information, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Budget, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Budget, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Building Acquisition Info, 1985-1989 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Building Budget, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Cal Scott, S. Winfield, March 1977 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Cartoon Correspondence, circa 1970s (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Catholic University Urban Teacher Corps, August 11, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Center Theatre Group, April 13, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Children's Theatre Love Letters, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Chris Keene, February 20, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Christmas Play - Budget and Schedule, Undated (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Clair Breault Letter - Montreal City Teacher's Workshop, July - December 1969 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Col. E Brooke Lee Jr. High School, July 13, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - The Commonwealth of Massachusetts, January 2, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Conservatory Correspondence, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Contacts, 1969-1970 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Copies of Contracts, 1970-1971 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Corcoran Rob Alexander - Consultant, July - October 1969 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Corporate Fundraising, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - Children's Theatre, 1967-1968 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence on Bob's European Trip, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence with Possible Venues, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence - Advisory Council, 1981-1982 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence - Nabil Sawelka and Robert Alexander, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence Received, 1986-1987 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence Sent, 1986-1987 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence - Robert Alexander, circa 1970s (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - CSAP Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Cultural Alliance of Greater Washington - American Arts Alliance, 1981-1982 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Danny Ditner Correspondence, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - D.C Teachers College, March 5, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - DC Commission - Public Forum Correspondence, Sample Forms, and 804s, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - DC Commission of the Arts and Humanities Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Delaware Valley College, Thomas Nelson Community College, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Department of Health Education and Welfare, DC Summer Workshop, August 25, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Development Correspondence, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - District of Columbia Teacher's College, June 12, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Earned Budget Incomes, 1984-1985 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Earned Income, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Earned Income Outline, 1984-1985 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Earned Income Updates, 1988-1989 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Elspeth Budget, 1981-1982 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - End of Season Info (Misc), 1989-1990 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Europe Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Expense Records - Living Stage and Curriculum Enrichment Program, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Expense Report - Boston University, 1972-1973 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Fan Mail - School Program, 1967-1968 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Financial Documents, 1983-1984 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Financial Documents, 1988-1989 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Foundation Target, 1982-1983 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Fund Drive, February 1984 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Fund Drive/Contributor Info, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Fundraising Letters, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Gallaudet College and Warren Wilson College, February 1976 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - General Ledgers Earned Income (Old Pages), 1985-1987 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - General Ledgers Trial Balance, 1988-1989 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - George Mason University, November 15, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - George Mason University, 1974-1976 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Goddard/Cambridge, May 27, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Goddard/Cambridge, September 10, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Head Start Ida Kolman - New Hampshire Vermont, 1968-1969 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - HEW Continuation Proposal, 1979-1980 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - HEW End of the Year Report, September 30, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - HEW Continuation Proposal, 1980-1981 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Himmelfarb Letter, October 20, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Hubert H. Humphrey, November 8, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Hudson City School District, July 20, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Hudson City School District, Col. Joseph M. Belt Jr. High, July 22, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Hunter's College, B.A.M, Jan 18-28, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Immaculate Conception, H.W. Longfellow School, 1972-1975 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Income from Workshops and Special Contracts, 1970-1971 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Income and Expenses from Workshops, 1971-1972 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Income from Workshops, 1972-1973 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Income and Expenses from Workshops, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Inner Voices, June 23, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - January Working Plan, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Joan Mondale, December 5, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Joan St. Germain and Laure V. McKenzie, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Kean College, February 15, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Ken Kitch Memos, circa 1970s (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Lesley College, May 23, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Looking Glass Theatre Aberdeen Jr. High, January 14, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Lorton Report, June 19, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Lorton Voices, January 11, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 10)